(Leonard:)This is fun, huh?
(Leonard:)We get to see our friend
throw out the first pitch,
(Leonard:)have a hot dog,
watch the game.
(Sheldon:)Whoa.
(Sheldon:)Nobody said anything
about watching the game.
(Amy:)Sheldon, what
did you expect?
(Sheldon:)I expected to see Howard throw
the baseball, finish my hot dog,
(Sheldon:)and hightail it across
the street to Disneyland
(Sheldon:)just in time for Mickey's
Soundsational Parade.
(Amy:)I'll tell you what.
(Amy:)If we stay, I'll buy you
cotton candy and a bobblehead.
(Sheldon:)Who's the bobblehead of?
(Amy:)Does it matter?
(Sheldon:)No, as long as it bobbles.
(Bernadette:)Howie, I am so proud of you.
(Howard:)Thanks.
I'm proud of me, too.
Mm-hmm.
(Man:)You ready?
(Howard:)Let's do it.
(Howard:)All right.
(Howard:)Wish me luck.
(Bernadette:)Go get 'em.
ANNOUNCER (over P.A.):
Ladies and gentlemen,
in honor of Space Day at
Angel Stadium, the first pitch
(Stadium Announcer:)will be thrown out by NASA
astronaut Howard Wolowitz.